ゴンが　ネフェルピトーに 持てる力の全てをたたきつけ
Tell the boss...
とどめを刺した頃
I won't go back until I settle up
メルエムは　プフ　ユピーと共に
with that chain user.
何かが足りぬ
The boss sells every item after
admiring it for a while.
だが　それが何かが…
The Scarlet Eyes should be no exception. That is all I know.
分からぬ。
But keep this in mind.
俺だって　あの娘を王に 会わせるのは　賛成じゃ　ねえ
I asked if you wanted to team up, but I was not suggesting that
we fight side by side. Merely that we exchange information,
in a give-and-take relationship.
どうやら 何か足りぬという焦燥。
If it ceases to be beneficial to either party, there will be no further
obligation to cooperate. Simple enough, yes? What do you say?
それも記憶喪失のもたらす 症候群の一つに すぎぬのかもしれぬ。
I'll be here tomorrow,
at the same time.
王のご記憶は　見ることによって 正しく思い出されております。
So, what do we do now?
ならば　必要なご記憶は
The leader is probably dead.
これから全て取り戻せます。
And we haven't completed the mission...
選別の決行は１２時だったな。
Shouldn't we report this to the boss? That little girl's our boss in name alone.
はっ しかし　前倒しは十分可能です。
It was someone else who hired us.
９時までには　残る全人民が
Light Nostrade, her father.
宮殿前の平野を埋め尽くします。 あっ。
He gave the orders, and the leader received them.
どうした？
But the leader was the only one
who knew how to contact him.
騒がれるのも厄介ですし 私は分身を呼び寄せ
It seems we have no choice but to report
what's happened to the boss.
催眠をかけてまいります。
Boss... Boss.
そうだな…　ピトーを捜そう。
What time is it?
今の俺じゃ メルエム様の護衛すら ままならないしな。
It's 2 AM. Huh? What about the auction?! It's been called off. Huh?
ピトー…。
Called off? Why?
何か思い出されましたか？
The auction was attacked by thieves. Huh?
そうか　王には　まだ ピトーのことを 言っていなかったか。
Baise, Ivlenkov, and Tocino
died during the attack. What?
お分かりになりますか？
We can't reach the leader,
so he's probably done for. No way.
うむ　護衛軍３名の１人。
What about the mummy? Was it really stolen?
姿も鮮明に浮かぶ。
I wanted it so much...
なぜ　今の今まで 思い出せなかったのかが
The Mafia community moved the
merchandise to a safe location.
不思議なほどにな。
Oh, that's great! So when is the next auction?
映像からだけじゃなく 言葉からも記憶が戻る
We don't yet know. What? Why not?
あれの名前も出せない 要注意だな
In any event, the leader
handled all communication, so we don't know anything.
うまくピトーを 説得できるかが鍵
We cannot act until we have orders. I don't know anything about that.
分かってるよ　口止めだな
So, ask Daddy. His number's on my phone.
まただ
You're the most experienced member left. You should be the leader.
)
I'm not the leader type.
あっ　そうだ
Perhaps we should take a vote, to be fair?
余は　ピトーに
We need to make the call quickly.
何か　頼んだ
I vote for Kurapika. He was the one who
apprehended the bandit, and he has shown excellent judgment.
ユピー。 はっ。 ピトーを連れてまいれ　早急にだ。
I believe he would make the best leader. No objections here.
I vote for Kurapika.
はっ。
That's that...
メルエム様は　どうされますか？
You make the call.
まだ　周りには 敵が残っておりますが。
I understand. As the interim leader,
I'll call Mr. Nostrade.
そうだな 余もピトーを捜しがてら 残党狩りと行くか。
This is only until we confirm
what's become of Dalzollene.
はっ　まずい
Any final decision will be
Mr. Nostrade's to make.
王　それは…。
I never expected to get
a chance so soon...
ただの余興だ。 敵から得られる情報もあろうが。 しかし 我々も　そばにおりませんし
It would be inappropriate for
me to call him directly, so would you provide an
introduction, boss? Sure.
心して答えよ　プフ。
Hello? Is it true that Dalzollene has been killed?
余が　万が一にも
I find that hard to believe. He is a Nen user.
賊に 後れを取る恐れがあると申すか？
He's trained to withstand ten gunshots without sustaining injury.
いえ　めっそうもございません。
I believe we should get your daughter out of
Yorknew City immediately.
こ…　これほどとは！
I agree with your assessment,
but my daughter also has a say.
王…　メルエム様は
My top priority is her safety.
唯一無二の存在 間違いございません！
I understand. I'm on my way now. I should arrive by tomorrow evening.
その圧倒的たるオーラは 潜伏していたナックル達に
Here is your first order. Keep an eye on Neon until I arrive.
完璧な絶望を植え付けた
Understood.
こ…　これは 俺達がどうにかできる レベルじゃ　ねえ！
Your father will arrive tomorrow night. Really? Yay!
いや　もう　これは 国家レベルの武力が要る
I'll get him to buy me lots of clothes. You are to wait in your room until then.
メレオロン　逃げるぞ！
What?
マジか？ 大マジだ！
I want to see the casino...
群衆に紛れて　ペイジンへ戻る！
Stay here with the boss. Huh? S-Sure...
キルアやイカルゴ達は どうする！
I'll be downstairs, investigating.
恐らく　ポットクリンを 憑けるまではやれるさ。
That building you were in is owned by
だがな…。
a dummy corporation for
the Nostrade Family.
ポットクリンは　俺が 半径５０ｍ以内にいなけりゃ
Can you get a list of buildings the Nostrade Family owns in this area?
カウントしねえんだ！
Of course!
あいつの…　あの５０ｍ以内。
I can also see if anyone's checked
in using the Nostrade name.
おめぇに　ボス並みの 肺活量がなきゃ無理だって！
Here, I brought more beer.
事情が変わったんだ！
Oh, thanks.
もうバレてんだ！ お前と俺の能力。
Here.
敵にな！
You should get a Hunter License, Uvo.
対策なんて いくらでも立てられちまう。 俺が　ばかだった！
You can get all kinds of
information from this website, as long as you have the money.
俺達が　やらなきゃいけないのは 会長の敗北を協会に伝えて
Unlike you guys, I dislike
the idea of money. If there's something I want, I take it.
事後の策を 早急に実行してもらうこと！
How splendid... You are the model thief!
早く！
Here we go. They own two other buildings.
復讐と任務
And there are three hotels
where members are staying...
メレオロンとナックルの 間にある動機の違いが ２人の歩幅と速度を変えた
Well, this should be a short search. Thanks.
その時…
Wh-What was that for?!
まさに閃光と等しい速度で
Well, I'm off, then.
メルエムの「円」が 宮殿の周囲を照らした
What about the beer? You guys can finish it. Make sure you dispose of the body.
近くに２人いた　という理由で
Huh? Don't get careless.
まずナックルが…
Yeah.
メレオロンが倒された
Family members?
消えた。
What's that? A list of buildings owned
by the Nostrade Family?
あっ。
There's a list of Family members...
此奴らには　後で話を聞く。 その後は　好きにせい。
I didn't know this information was available. This website can only be
accessed by pro Hunters.
余の「円」に　オーラでもって 過敏な反応を示した能力者は
With this information,
they can locate this room. A website for pro Hunters...
あと２人。
Then if one of the enemies is a pro Hunter...
その２人のどちらかが
We need to take the boss
and find a different room.
気絶したコムギを 背負っているはず
Eh? In the same hotel? It's faster and avoids needless movement.
どうする？　どうする？
But we cannot use fake names. We'll have Melody or Basho register the room.
はっ！
Make sure everyone,
especially the boss, stays inside.
止めねば　王を
Got it.
王！
Don't check out of this one.
余興ならば　もう少し 楽しむ必要がございましょう。
Huh? You can't mean to...
勝負をいたしませんか？ 勝負？
I-I don't think that's a Family member.
クッ　また…
He's a bodyguard for the boss' daughter... Daughter?
勝負…　勝負…
Yeah... She's a strange one who
collects human body parts. Eyeballs and organs...
勝負…　勝負…
Oh, and she's an incredibly
accurate fortune teller. Fortune teller? She has a long list of Mafia clients...
勝負とは？ ユピーと私が　ピトーを捜し出し
Some community elders basically worship her.
メルエム様は 残り２人の能力者を捜し出す。
After all, our boss
どちらが早く見つけ出すか…　か。 はっ。
made his fortune by using
his daughter's power. Hey... C-Cut me some slack?
けど　お前は鱗粉　飛ばしに 行くんじゃねえのか？
I told you everything I know. Please spare me!
ですから　私が残りの人民に 催眠をかけるまでの時間
Someone who can see the future...
メルエム様には　ここで お待ちいただきたいのです。
She knew the attack would happen?
王と賊との間に
The boss was right.
天地よりも高い 実力差があることは　既に明らか。 ただ見つけて捕らえるだけならば ほんの数秒。
There weren't any traitors.
余興にすら　なりませぬ。
Currently, we have a 3,000,000 diamond
対して　我々が捜すピトーは
and 2,400,000 Jenny in leftover cash.
瞬間移動に似た能力を 駆使する敵と戦闘中で
And we also have the 2,750,000
Jenny from the arm wrestling.
現在いる場所も不明です。
That gives us a total of around 8,000,000.
その差を埋めるため 我々に時間と もう一つ　ハンディキャップを 頂きたいのです。
We need to turn this into at least 9 billion, the minimum opening bid for Greed Island...
もう一つ…　何だ？
I don't see how we can manage that
through legitimate channels.
「円」を使えるのは　あと一回だけ
I wouldn't call that arm wrestling legitimate.
…というのは　いかがでしょう？
All the challengers toward the end were
half desperate losers trying for revenge.
面白い。
That's fine.
That was my goal.
その勝負　受けよう。
We want as many people as
possible to embellish the tale.
ありがとうございます。
What do you mean?
やった！　この時間を使い 完璧に娘を抹殺する！
The arm wrestling was meant as bait. Bait? To draw out the moles.
せっかくの遊びだ 余からも提案がある。
Moles? Why do we want moles? Pipe down now.
I'll explain everything.
それぞれの望み　一つ　かなえよう。
Come on down!
あっ。 あっ。
Let's have some
conditional auctioning fun!
はっ。 はっ　ありがたき　お言葉。
We have a diamond worth 3,000,000. The winner will be determined
through arm wrestling.
では　メルエム様が 勝利された時は？ 余が勝った場合
The first person to beat this
boy wins the diamond.
お主達が余に隠していること 話してもらおう。
You must pay a 10,000-Jenny entry fee. What? He's just a kid. I'll give it a shot.
うっ！ うっ！
Don't bother.
王…。 黙れ。
Over twenty ended up with broken arms. Seriously?!
言ったはずだ。 お主達と余は　既に異体同心。
The stories are spreading nicely. In that case...
お主達が強く発する 後ろ暗い感情に
Move.
余が感づかぬとでも思ったか？
Oh, do we have our first challenger? No.
だが同時に より強く発する　余への忠心。
I already know that my man
can't beat your kid. I was watching yesterday. Then what do you want?
それがなければ とうに首をはねておるわ。
Interested in making some real money? Meaning? I know where you can make big bucks
うぅ…
instead of the pocket change
you're getting here.
何か事情があるのだろう あえて聞かぬ。
You can make hundreds... No, thousands of times more.
望むものを手に入れ 秘め事は守り通せる。
Are they moles? Yeah, looks like we landed a big fish.
これ以上の条件はあるまい。
Huh? Fish? Don't you mean moles?
余に勝てれば…　だがな。
Stop talking.
It doesn't matter!
暇つぶしとは思えぬ目だな プフよ。
Oh! I can feel the bloodlust.
プフが散布を終え
The arm wrestling competition here
accepts all comers, and it pays out.
ここに戻って来たら 余が始動する。 それでよいな？
The spectators bet on each match, and the winner receives ten
percent of all bets placed.
はっ。
We're talking billions bet on each match.
先に　この部屋に標的を連れて 戻って来たほうの勝利。
That would mean millions with each win!
仮に　ピトーが 単独で戻って来た場合は
You could win even more... I'll be taking fifty percent of your
earnings as my commission.
ピトーに趣旨を説明し お主達から隠れるよう指示しよう。
Fifty percent? Isn't that a little high?
御意。
You can't participate
unless I enter your name.
あらかじめ言っておこう。
Besides, you can bet your own money.
「円」で感知した能力者は タコと荷物を背負った人間だ。
You'll get great odds with that kid, and earn back your stake
a hundred times over. That's right! I'm in!
勝たねば… いや　勝つのは当然！
Go, Gon! Huh? Well? Any other challengers?
問題は　ピトーと娘の処遇
Got one right here! This kid's up for the challenge.
では…。
Very well.
ピトーは　どこに行ったと思う？
Sorry, but the arm wrestling is canceled!
大丈夫　すぐ戻って来るはずです。
We'll be doing some
conditional auctioning now!
あなたは引き返して　西塔の周囲で ピトーを張っててください。
Why was it canceled? U-Uh, I don't know.
王に近づかせないように。 お前　散布中は 分身　使えねえんだろ？
To win, you must play
hide-and-seek!
それじゃ 時間のハンデの意味が…。 私を信じて！　頼みます！
Hide-and-seek? We'll start by passing out flyers!
うん…。
Examine the pictures on the flyer.
ハァ　ハァ　ハァ…。
Those seven people are your targets!
何てこと
Hey, that girl with glasses was...
何て　すさまじいオーラ
Yep, she arm wrestled me.
２人は　死… いいえ　きっと生きている
Hey, are they the ones responsible
for what happened last night?
気絶させられただけよ
Yeah, you mean the attack on the auction?
ゴンは？ キルアに担がれている 髪が長い…　別人!?
In order to win the bid, you must capture and deliver a target to us.
いいえ　水晶は この２人しか映していない あれはゴン
For each target brought in, you will receive a nice sum of 2 billion Jenny!
私が見ていない間に何が？ ピトーは？
There is no time limit.
とにかく　こっちには 戻らないで　お願い！
It doesn't matter if the
target is dead or alive. Please contact us once
you've captured one!
プフは 群衆に鱗紛をまいてる
Two billion each? If we catch them all, we'd have 14 billion!
毒？ 王の近くに いてくれたほうが助かるのに
It'll cost you 5 million Jenny to participate!
とにかく 私からは遠いし　逆方向
We're joining in, right? Yeah...
あの「円」の後 すぐ発動した「ウインクブルー」
Yeah, that's right.
I'll fax you the information.
ナックルとメレオロンを抱えて プフのそばにいた
Search the Net for information. We'll pay for anything concrete.
その間　ほんの数秒
We need to hurry.
次は　私かイカルゴ
There's no rush. They won't be able to catch our targets.
いつ　王が背後にいても おかしくない
Huh? After all, the Mafia's having
trouble handling them.
早く！ もっと遠くへ逃げなければ！
What do you mean?
王が もう一度　「円」を使う前に
This conditional auction is
nothing but a bounty hunt.
ここしかない
In other words, the Mafia is admitting that, alone,
it can't capture these targets.
平野では　あの「円」を使われたら 絶対　逃げ切れない
You have a point...
この奥深くならば 「円」は届かないかもしれない
They were willing to suspend
everything to track them down.
けど　袋のねずみなのも確か
I just heard that the underground
auction was attacked last night.
王が　しばらく動かないことに 賭けて宮殿の外へ逃げるべき？
The underground auction?! Was it them?
何の根拠もないのに？
That's why there's a
reward for their heads?
ハッ　ハァ　ハァ…。
Yep, they must be nuts to
steal from the Mafia. And we already know who would
be crazy enough for that.
入るぞ　急げ！
Oh, right...
ええ　でも…。 早く！
What's Kurapika up to?
そのつもりで来たんだろ？ もう一度　「円」が来たら しまいだぞ！
Yeah, he should be in the city, but he hasn't made contact. I'll call him.
そうか　メレオロン達は 捕まっちまったか。
He isn't answering. Is he working?
桁違いだったからな　あれは。
Working? I heard that he's been
working as a bodyguard.
どうして ２人は生かされたと思う？ えっ？　それは…。
Probably for some VIP... He's trying to track down the Scarlet Eyes, so it must be someone in the underworld.
多分　生きているっていう程度の 私の願望よ。
What if he was guarding that
person at the auction house, and got caught up in the attack?
生きてるよ。
He wouldn't have been
caught up in the attack.
恐らく　トレードのため。
If the Troupe attacked, he'd be
actively tracking them down.
キルアの言っていた人質交換ね。
It's possible that he's already
captured two or three.
罠にかけてやる。
I hope you're right...
勝負…
for the chance to exact revenge
upon the Phantom Troupe. Their battle is about to start.